gu95.com 2017-10-27

# Above.com Privacy Policy

Above.com Pty Ltd understands the importance of your privacy on and off the Internet. In every action we take, Above lives up to our strict privacy statement. Whenever Above handles personal information, regardless of where this occurs, we take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy.

Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the many offerings on our website.

Above collects and retains all personal information about you that is in relation to your use of this service. This includes but not limited to your: Name, Contact Details and Billing Details. You authorize us to use this data for marketing purposes for any other Above or associated service, or associated entities.

Above may, from time to time, send you an email regarding our products or services. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information or at any point in time.

Above does not sell or provide to third parties any personal information collected as part of your use of this service.

Above does not sell or provide to third parties any data derived from this service, aggregated or not that can be tied or linked to you personally or your account.

Above in the course of providing this service uses various means to access and obtain data in your specified Parking Services accounts. The data that is provided by you or extracted only contains relevant traffic data points relating to your domains as used in the Above reporting. No other personal details are accessed such as: contact details, payment details, payment history, revenue share or tax information from your third party Parking companies accounts. Ownership of any data provided or extracted from third party accounts, remains solely with you.

By accepting these terms and conditions, you agree to the use of your personal information as outlined above.

This policy may change from time to time, so please check back frequently.
